"Dr. Cooper has taken
a relatively boring subject
"and managed to make it
completely insufferable.
(Leonard:)Plus, he looks
like a giant insect."
(Howard:)Look. Listen to this one.
"Does Einstein's theory
explain why time flies
"when you're having fun,
"but when you're listening
to Dr. Cooper,
it falls out of the sky, dead?"
(Raj:)Ooh, somebody took pictures
(Raj:)and uploaded them
to their Flickr account.
(Leonard:)Wow.
(Leonard:)How do you get an
entire lecture hall
(Leonard:)to flip you off
at the same time?
(Howard:)Apparently, if you're Sheldon,
(Howard:)all you need
to do is turn your back.
(Penny:)Hey, Leonard,
is your wi-fi down?
(Penny:)I can't get on.
(Leonard:)Oh, Sheldon changed
the password.
(Leonard:)It's now
"Penny is a freeloader."
(Leonard:)No spaces.
(Penny:)Thanks.
What are you guys doing?
(Leonard:)Sheldon gave a lecture
at the university tonight.
(Leonard:)We're reading
the reviews.
(Penny:)Oh. How'd he do?
(Howard:)Well, picture the Hindenburg
meets Chernobyl
meets Three Mile Island
meets Tron 2.
(Penny:)That bad, huh?
(Leonard:)Read this woman's tweet.